The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Another Soul Transformation ?
Junior Ceng Niu,
As I told you,
today
is the day you die.
My spiritual energy is in chaos
and my Origin Soul is damaged.
Even when using the celestial sword
I am not as strong as when I fought Red Butterfly.
This Heaven-Sealing Formation is extremely complex,
it must be some kind of ancient inheritance.
I can't escape it in a short time.
Master, run !
This truly is a fine sword.
It even contains a Sword Spirit !
Good.
This sword can be yours
but the flag that can summon tribulations
belongs to me.
Fine,
but I am taking back the star compass
that belonged to my clan.
Of course.
Giant Demon Clan ?
Giant Demon Clan Ancestor\NEarly stage Soul Transformation
This old man is indeed from the Giant Demon Clan.
Back in the Celestial Realm,
you stole the star compass from our young master, Chi Hu.
But today
I will take it back !
Two Soul Transformation old monsters joining hands
just to take my life...
It's an honor,
I will be sure to remember it.
Indeed,
you should remember it well.
However,
you will leave your artifacts behind !
That's a good artifact !
I'm out of spiritual energy...
Wait !
Ancestor,
please let this Junior
kill this person
to avenge myself.
Chi Hu...
Ceng Niu,
accept your death !
Spiritual energy ?
Brother Ceng,
escape to the southeast !
Chi Hu,
what are you doing !?
Go, now !
Ancestor,
the star compass is something I gifted to Ceng Niu,
not something he stole.
Ceng Niu saved my life many times in the Celestial Realm.
I, Chi Hu, am a man of my word.
How could I abandon him just like that ?
Step aside !
The star compass is useless to our clan.
So what if I give it to Ceng Niu ?
You took his flying sword, isn’t that enough ?
If you weren’t the junior with the purest Giant Demon blood,
I would kill you today, you ungrateful brat !
Once we return,
you will be punished to 100 years
of constant pain from body refinement !
I, Chi Hu, am an honorable man
so I can’t do something so heartless.
Brother Ceng,
I...
tried my best...
This formation is mysterious,
it's even able to prevent me from entering
the Heaven Defying Bead.
In the southeast
there's a forest
rich in Yin energy.
Indeed,
if I can escape the formation there,
I can flee into a spatial rift.
Junior,
before a Soul Transformation cultivator,
a mere Soul Formation cultivator
cannot survive.
Li Yuanfeng's\NTea Domain
A Soul Transformation domain ?
This is my Tea Domain.
The fragrance of tea
allows me to savor the flavors of Life.
The pot hides a universe
and the leaves represent Spring and Autumn.
Life and Death Domain,
activate !
With tea as my companion
I grasped the meaning of Life.
Before the domain of a Soul Transformation cultivator,
your domain
is pathetic.
We’ve wasted enough time,
after killing him
I have other matters to attend to.
Fellow cultivator Li,
make your move.
Since you refuse to act,
does that mean you are afraid of Mount Suzaku ?
Forget it,
since I initiated this
I’ll take care of it myself.
He's here at last...
The Heaven-Sealing Formation ?
If I didn’t already know this formation,
it would’ve been really hard
for me to enter.
The Corpse Sect ?
Although they’re only Early stage Soul Transformation,
it’s said that Giant Demons who reach Soul Transformation
awaken their bloodline's power.
I'd prefer not to provoke them too much.
Ceng Niu,
do you have nothing better to do
than getting yourself into trouble ?
You two old fossils,
aren't you ashamed of bullying a Soul Formation junior ?
I’m taking this person away.
Fellow cultivator...
Scram !
A mere Early stage Soul Transformation
whose cultivation was forcibly raised
is unworthy
to speak to this old man.
I refuse,
he must die.
And his corpse
belongs to me !
You’re not from the Corpse Sect,
what use do you have for a corpse ?
That's because...
When I arrived,
Wang Lin was already dead.
But a strand of his soul fled to the Foreign Battlefield.
I pursued it
but after decades of searching,
I gave up.
I fear that
the Heaven Defying Bead is also...
Is anyone else
aware of this matter ?
Of course not,
I’ve erased all witnesses’ memories.
Only I and the Envoy
sent to Zhao's Heaven's Tower
know the truth.
Good,
very good...
A treasure wanted by even the Cultivation Alliance
can’t just disappear like that !
If we offer the Heaven Defying Bead to the Cultivation Alliance,
we will be promoted to a rank 6 cultivation country
and gifted our own cultivation planet !
When that happens,
my Giant Demon Clan
will have the ability to have Ascendant level cultivators.
I searched for Wang Lin’s whereabouts for years.
Only after Chi Hu returned from the Celestial Realm
did I learn by coincidence
that Ceng Niu was Wang Lin.
To prevent the country of Suzaku from interfering,
I waited for the right moment.
When Li Yuanfeng came to me,
I used the star compass as an excuse
to join him to kill Wang Lin.
Even if Wang Lin dies,
as long as I have his corpse,
I can get my hand on the Heaven Defying Bead.
I have my own reasons.
Scram !
You dare ?!
Giant Axe
Border of the\Ncountry of Pilu
Sun Tai came to save me
but he doesn't have good intentions.
However, it was the only way to escape the formation.
A thousand-year slave seal...
It's only been a few years and you caused such a disaster !
This time, I’ll seal you completely
so you won’t drag me down with you.
Seal !
Do you really think I'm afraid to fight you ?!
How ?!
My cultivation...
Wang Lin's avatar\N3rd layer of Qi Condensation
How did this happen ?
Li Yuanfeng’s Tea Domain
and Sun Tai’s sealing mark
must have combined into a powerful restriction
that's draining my spiritual energy completely.
If this goes on,
I’ll revert into a powerless mortal.
The last time I was this badly injured
was when Teng Huayuan destroyed my body.
Who would have thought that centuries later,
I would encounter such a disaster again.
I’ve been cautious every step of the way
but still ended up at the mercy of others.
Ceng Niu
is mine !
Explode !
When Soul Transformation cultivators fight for real,
it’s a battle of life and death.
Are you ready ?
Fighting a Middle stage Soul Transformation is exhausting
but Wang Lin is crucial to the Giant Demon Clan.
In that case,
I have no choice.
Now that it’s come to this
you’ve forced my hand !
Soul Transformation cultivators rarely fight to the death.
Once our celestial spiritual energy is depleted,
it cannot be replenished.
But since you insist,
this old man will face you
with celestial spiritual energy !
The might of celestial spiritual energy
is exclusive to Soul Transformation and above.
I will never let the chance
to revive my clan slip away !
This old man is Middle stage Soul Transformation.
Even with your Giant Demon Clan’s bloodline,
you cannot bridge the gap between us.
Still refusing to yield ?
My Lightning Domain
was gained after I paid a great price
to cultivate a century on the Heavenly Thunder Planet !
Sun Tai's\NThunder Domain
You mere Early stage Soul Transformation,
will die now !
I’ll take this person away.
and return him in 7 days.
Not possible !
If I let you take him,
it's the same as giving you my Origin Soul.
You dare to sneak up on him under my nose !?
The seal on this kid is only half-complete.
I must finish off these two quickly
or else
something might go wrong.
Since reaching Soul Transformation,
this is my first time using my bloodline's power.
You...
take my attack !
Turn !
Demon Child,
come out !
Demon Child\NMiddle stage Soul Transformation
Turn !
Demon Child,
kill him !
Turn !
With my Early stage Soul Transformation cultivation,
my bloodline's power has no attack power.
It can only teleport the target to a distant planet.
If I keep fighting,
I'm afraid my soul will dissipate...
I played all my cards
but they didn't amount to anything.
It was all in vain...
My cultivation is still falling...
My spiritual energy is leaving my body...
The path of cultivation
truly is
unpredictable.
In 8 years,
Wan’er will face the law of the heavens again.
8 years...
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.